{
	"__comment": "These are ROT13 encoded so you don't spoil yourself.",
	"questions": [
		{"prompt": "No Place", "answer": "N fznyy ivyyntr va Pbhagl Qheunz va Ratynaq gung qbrf npghnyyl rkvfg. Ubzr gb na njneq jvaavat erny nyr cho."},
		{"prompt": "Principality of Sealand", "answer": "N zvpebangvba juvpu pynvzf na bssfuber cyngsbez va gur Abegu Frn nf vgf greevgbel. Vgf cevzr zvavfgre uverq zrepranevrf gb yrnq na nggnpx ba vg bire qvfnterrzragf jvgu vgf xvat."},
		{"prompt": "Reality Checkpoint", "answer": "N pnfg veba ynzcbfg va Pnzoevqtr. Vg unf inevbhf gurbevrf nf gb gur bevtvaf bs vgf anzr, yvxr znexvat gur obhaqnel orgjrra gur havirefvgl nern bs Pnzoevqtr, be erzvaqvat gur qehax gb rafher gurl pna jnyx abeznyyl orsber cnffvat gur cbyvpr fgngvba."},
		{"prompt": "Spreuerhofstrasse", "answer": "Gur aneebjrfg fgerrg va gur jbeyq, nppbeqvat gb gur Thvaarff Jbeyq Erpbeqf. Vg vf 31pz ng vgf aneebjrfg, naq 50pz ng vgf jvqrfg."},
		{"prompt": "A Mountain", "answer": "N zbhagnva va Nevmban jvgu n ynetr 'N' ba vg. Ohvyg bhg bs tenavgr ol Havirefvgl bs Nevmban fghqragf va gur 1910f."},
		{"prompt": "Centralia", "answer": "N gbja va Craaflyinavn jvgu n pbny zvar sver gung unf orra oheavat fvapr 1962. Ubhfrq bayl 7 erfvqragf va 2013."},
		{"prompt": "Jackass Flats", "answer": "N grfg fvgr sbe ahpyrne cbjrerq ebpxrg ratvarf. Pbiref nobhg 120 fdhner zvyrf."},
		{"prompt": "Gum Wall", "answer": "N oevpx jnyy pbirerq va purjvat thz. Jnf pyrnarq va 2015, naq gur svefg nqqvgvbaf bs zber thz jrer zrzbevnyf gb gur erprag Cnevf nggnpxf."},
		{"prompt": "M-185", "answer": "N uvtujnl juvpu onaf zbgbe iruvpyrf. Ba na vfynaq, naq guhf qvfpbaarpgrq sebz gur erfg bs gur ebnq argjbex."},
		{"prompt": "Delaware Wedge", "answer": "N genpg bs ynaq obeqrevat 3 Nzrevpna fgngrf, perngrq ol gur fubegpbzvatf bs fheirlvat grpuavdhrf ng gur gvzr jura gur obhaqnevrf jrer qrsvarq."},
		{"prompt": "Fordlandia", "answer": "N qvfgevpg va Oenmvy. Perngrq ol Urael Sbeq nf na vaqhfgevny gbja gb fbhepr uvf pbzcnal jvgu phygvingrq ehoore. Jnf arneyl nonaqbarq hagvy gur rneyl 2000f, naq vf abj ubzr gb nobhg 3000 crbcyr va 2017."},
		{"prompt": "Yo", "answer": "Lb vf n zbovyr pbzzhavpngvbaf ncc eryrnfrq va 2014. Vg pna fraq bayl bar zrffntr: gur jbeq 'lb'."},
		{"prompt": "JASON reactor", "answer": "WNFBA jnf n ahpyrne erfrnepu ernpgbe vafgnyyrq ng gur Eblny Aniny Pbyyrtr gb genva crefbaary vaibyirq va ahpyrne fhoznevar cebchyfvba."},
		{"prompt": "The Great Stink", "answer": "Na 19gu praghel rirag va juvpu gur nzbhag bs fuvg va gur Gunzrf jnf fb chatrag gung vg vagresrerq jvgu npghny tbireazrag unccravatf."},
		{"prompt": "Zenzizenzizenzic", "answer": "Bofbyrgr zngurzngvpny abgngvba sbe gur rvtugu cbjre bs n ahzore. Bevtvangrq va nobhg 1557."},
		{"prompt": "Smoot", "answer": "Gur fzbbg vf n abafgnaqneq havg bs yratgu perngrq nf n cneg bs n cenax ol ZVG fghqragf. Vg vf anzrq nsgre Byvire E Fzbbg, jub ynvq qbja ercrngrqyl ba gur Uneineq Oevqtr gb hfr uvz nf n zrnfher bs gur yratgu bs gur oevqtr."}
	]
}